deanza.edu 2003-06-29

# Web Site Privacy Statement

### Privacy Statement

De Anza College has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: http://www.deanza.edu/. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

Our site's college registration forms require users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code or age). The student's contact information is used to contact the student when necessary. 

Financial information that is collected is used to check the user's qualifications for college registration and to bill the user for class sessions. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected to verify the user's identity. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site to help us determine future requirements for the Web site. 

This site contains links to other sites. De Anza College is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address). The visitor's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. We do not release or distribute this information. 

**Public Forums**  
This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Children's Guidelines**  

  1. We do NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent. 
  2. We do NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent. 
  3. We do NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent. 
  4. We do NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. 
  5. We do NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity. 

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact:  
Terri O'Connor  
De Anza College  
21250 Stevens Creek Boulevard  
Cupertino, CA   95014
